Register of the Socialist Workers Party records
Hoover Institution Archives
- CHRONOLOGICAL FILE, 1929-1989
  - Includes material on Canada, Peru, Bolivia, Chile, Argentina, Uruguay, Great Britain, Sweden, France, Czechoslovakia, India, Sri Lanka, Australia, and the anti-Vietnam War movement, 1972 (Box 23)
    - January-May (Folder 1)
    - June-December (Folder 2)
  - Includes material on Canada, Chile, Argentina, Sweden, France, Pakistan, Hong Kong, and New Zealand, 1973 (Folder 3)
  - Includes material on Canada, Mexico, Brazil, Great Britain, Sweden, France, Italy, Germany, India, Japan, Australia, and New Zealand, 1974 (Folder 4)
  - Includes material on France, Portugal, and India, 1975 (Folder 5)
  - Includes material on Argentina, Portugal, Angola, the Organizing Committee for the Reconstruction of the Fourth International, and the Leninist-Trotskyist Faction and International Majority Tendency within the Fourth International, 1976 (Folder 6)
  - Includes material on France, Spain, the United States (Socialist Union), political prisoners in Eastern Europe, and the Bolshevik Tendency within the Fourth International, and reminiscences of Michel Pablo, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Includes material on El Salvador, Costa Rica, Colombia, Ecuador, Peru, Bolivia, Argentina, Iceland, Ireland, Great Britain, France, Spain, Portugal, Lebanon, Vietnam, the Organizing Committee for the Reconstruction of the Fourth International, the Bolshevik Tendency, political prisoners in Eastern Europe, the women's movement, and the anti-nuclear movement, 1978
    - January-February (Folder 2)
    - March (Folder 3)
    - April-July (Folder 4)
    - August-December (Folder 5)
  - Includes material on France, Iran, and splits of the Bolshevik Faction and the Leninist-Trotskyist Tendency from the Fourth International, 1979 (Folder 6)
  - Includes material on Nicaragua, Bolivia, Afghanistan, and the Bolshevik Faction, 1980 (Folder 7)
  - Includes material on Peru, Bolivia, and Poland, 1981 (Folder 8)
  - Includes material on Poland, and the United States (Peter Camejo), 1982 (Folder 9)
  - Includes material on the United States (re speech by Jack Barnes of 31), and the women's movement, 1983. 1982 December (Folder 10)
  - Includes material on the United States (Fourth Internationalist Tendency, Socialist Action; Alan Gelfand case; general elections), 1984
    - January-September (Folder 11)
    - October-December (Folder 12)
  - Includes material on Mexico, and the United States (Fourth Internationalist Tendency, Socialist Action, Socialist Unity), 1985
    - January-July (Folder 13)
    - August (Folder 14)
    - September (Folder 15)
    - October-December (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Includes material on Canada, Great Britain, Palestine, Australia, the United States (Fourth Internationalist Tendency, Socialist Action, Socialist Unity; Library of Social History), and the women's movement, 1986
    - January-March (Folder 2)
    - April (Folder 3)
    - May-June (Folder 4)
    - July-August (Folder 5)
    - September-November (Folder 6)
  - Includes material on Israel, the United States (Socialist Workers Party relations with the Fourth International), and the women's movement, 1987 (Folder 7)
  - Includes material on the United States (lawsuit against the Federal Bureau of Investigation; Socialist Workers Party relations with the Fourth International), 1988 (Folder 8)
  - Includes material on the United States (Socialist Workers Party relations with the Fourth International), 1989 (Folder 9)
- GEOGRAPHICAL FILE, 1928-1989
  Records of the Socialist Workers Party's interactions with the Fourth International and its predecessors, classified by geographical area, including correspondence, notes, memoranda, reports, minutes, agenda, resolutions, theses, declarations, statements, circulars, and printed issuances. Arranged alphabetically by country. Other material relating to particular countries may be located in the CHRONOLOGICAL FILE
  - Argentina (Box 23)
    - General
      - 1939-1940 (Folder 7)
      - 1941 (Folder 8)
      - 1942 (Folder 9)
      - 1943-1945 (Folder 10)
      - 1946 (Folder 11)
      - 1947-1951 (Folder 12)
      - 1953-1955 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - 1959-1963 (Folder 2)
      - 1970 (Folder 3-4)
      - 1987 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Partido Obrero (Trotskista). Voz Proletaria. Vol. 13 no. 209 first fortnight), (1960 July (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous printed matter, 1960 (Folder 6)
  - Australia
    - General
      - 1937-1939 (Folder 7)
      - 1941-1944 (Folder 8)
      - 1945 (Folder 9)
      - 1946 (Folder 10)
      - 1947-1949 (Folder 11)
      - 1950-1973 (Folder 12)
      - 1982 (Box 58, Folder 11)
      - 1983 (Folder 12)
      - 1984-1985 (Folder 13)
      - 1986 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - 1987-1989 (Folder 2)
    - Labor Socialist Group (Box 24)
      - Untitled issuances, 1945 (Folder 13)
      - Socialist., 1945-1947 (Folder 14)
        Unnumbered (1945 December 8, 22, 1946 March 23); Vol. 1 no. 2 (1946 April 23), no. 3 (May 23), no. 4 (June 24), no. 8 (November 23), no. 10 (1947 January 10), no. 11 (February 10)
    - Revolutionary Workers Party. Fourth International. Unnumbered, (1945 June) (Folder 15)
    - Socialist Foundation
      - Southern Socialist Review., 1945 (Folder 16)
        Unnumbered (1945 July 17); new series no. 4 (August 13), no. 5 (August 27), no. 13 (December 30), no. 14 (1946 [1945--sic] January 22), no. 16 (March), no. 17 (April-May), no. 18 (May 15)
      - Southern Socialist International Digest. No. 22 (September), no. 23 (mid-September), no. 26 (December 1), 1946 (Folder 17)
      - Untitled issuances, 1945 (Folder 18)
    - Socialist League (Box 59)
      - Discussion Bulletin. Vol. 1 no. 1 (1987 February), no. 2 (July) (Folder 3)
      - Organiser. Unnumbered, (1987 July) (Folder 4)
      - Untitled issuance, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Socialist Workers Party [of Australia] (Box 59)
      - Constitution, 1979 (Folder 5)
      - Information Bulletin. No. 1, (1979 November) (Folder 6)
      - Party Organiser. Vol. 2 no. 4 (June), no. 6 (July), 1979 (Folder 7)
      - Socialist Worker. Vol. 3 no. 2, (1983 August) (Folder 8)
    - Solidarity
      - Dear Comrades... No. 1, (1987 January) (Folder 9)
      - F.I. News., 1986-1987 (Folder 10)
        No. 1 (1986 December), no. 2 (1987 January), no. 3 (April), no. 4 (May)
      - Newsletter. No. 2 (August), no. 3 (November), 1986 (Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous printed matter, 1944-1945 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Austria
    - General, 1947 (Folder 21)
    - Internationale Kommunisten Österreichs. Interne Mitteilungen. No. 2 (1947 February 5), no. 3 (March 4) (Folder 22)
    - Österreich Bulletin, (1939 March) (Folder 23)
  - Belgium (Box 25)
    - General
      - 1935-1937 (Folder 1)
      - 1945 (Folder 2)
      - 1946 (Folder 3)
      - 1947 (Folder 4)
      - 1948-1949 (Folder 5)
      - 1957-1973 (Folder 6)
    - Ligue Communiste Internationaliste. Bulletin Intérieur. No. 10, (1933 October) (Folder 7)
    - Parti Communiste Révolutionnaire. Congress documents, 1945 November (Folder 8)
  - Bolivia
    - 1941-1947 (Folder 9)
    - 1952-1953 (Folder 10)
    - 1954 (Folder 11)
    - 1955-1956 (Folder 12)
  - Brazil, 1941-1953 (Folder 13)
  - Bulgaria, 1946 (Folder 14)
  - Canada
    - General
      - 1928-1939 (Folder 15)
      - 1941-1943 (Folder 16)
      - 1944 (Folder 17)
      - 1945 (Folder 18)
      - 1946 (Folder 19)
      - 1947 (Folder 20)
      - 1948 (Folder 21)
      - 1949 (Folder 22)
      - 1950 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - 1951 (Folder 2)
      - 1952 (Folder 3)
      - 1953 (Folder 4)
      - 1954 (Folder 5)
      - 1955 (Folder 6)
      - 1956 (Folder 7)
      - 1957 (Folder 8)
      - 1958 (Folder 9)
      - 1959 (Folder 10)
      - 1960 (Folder 11)
      - 1961 (Folder 12)
      - 1962 (Folder 13)
      - 1963 (Folder 14)
      - 1964 (Folder 15)
      - 1965 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - 1966 (Folder 2)
      - 1967 (Folder 3)
      - 1968 (Folder 4)
      - 1969 (Folder 5)
      - 1970 (Folder 6)
      - 1971 (Folder 7)
      - 1972
        - January-June (Folder 8)
        - July (Folder 9-10)
        - August-December (Folder 11)
      - 1973
        - January-March (Folder 12)
        - April-June (Folder 13)
        - July-September (Box 28, Folder 1)
        - October-December (Folder 2)
      - 1974 (Folder 3)
      - 1975 (Folder 4)
      - 1980-1982 (Box 59, Folder 12)
      - 1983-1984 (Folder 13)
      - 1985 (Folder 14)
    - Alliance for Socialist Action. Bulletin
      - Vol. 1 no. 1 (December), 1984 (Folder 15)
      - Vol. 2 no. 1 (February), no. 2 (July), no. 3 (September); pre-convention series, no. 1 (September), no. 2 (October), no. 3 (November 7), 1985 (Folder 16)
    - Gauche Socialiste
      - Gauche Socialiste. Vol. 2 no. 1, (1985 Winter) (Folder 17)
      - Publications. Pamphlet and leaflet, 1985 (Folder 18)
    - League for Socialist Action/Ligue Socialiste Ouvrière (Box 28)
      - Political Committee minutes
        - 1954 (Folder 5)
        - 1955 (Folder 6)
        - 1956 (Folder 7)
        - 1959 (Folder 8)
        - 1960 (Folder 9)
        - 1961 (Folder 10)
        - 1962 (Folder 11)
        - 1963 (Folder 12)
        - 1964 (Folder 13)
        - 1965 (Folder 14)
        - 1966 (Folder 15)
        - 1967 (Folder 16)
        - 1968 (Folder 17)
        - 1969 (Folder 18)
        - 1970 (Folder 19)
        - 1971 (Folder 20)
        - 1972 (Folder 21)
        - 1973
          - January-August (Folder 22)
          - September (Box 29, Folder 1)
          - October-December (Folder 2)
        - 1974 (Folder 3)
      - Meetings file. Agenda, reports, draft resolutions, notes, and minutes
        - Convention, 1963 July (Folder 4)
        - Convention, 1966 May (Folder 5)
        - Convention, 1968 June-July (Folder 6)
        - Central Committee plenum, 1972 September (Folder 7)
        - Central Committee plenum, 1973 January (Folder 8)
        - Convention, (2 folders), 1973 April (Folder 9-10)
        - Young Socialist Alliance [United States] plenum, Report of Canadian representative, 1973 June (Folder 11)
        - Convention, 1973 December (Folder 12)
        - Central Committee plenum, 1974 January (Folder 13)
      - Discussion Bulletin. No. 1, (1972 June) (Folder 14)
    - Publications. Pamphlets and printed articles, 1968-1974 (Folder 15)
    - Liaison Committee for Reconstruction of the Fourth International in Canada. Bulletin no. 1 (1973 Autumn); Journal du Frap vol. 1 no. 11 (1973 October) (Folder 16)
    - Revolutionary Marxist Group
      - Minutes, 1974 (Folder 17)
      - Publications. Pamphlet and leaflet, 1973 (Folder 18)
    - Revolutionary Workers League/Ligue Ouvrière Révolutionnaire (Box 59)
      - Bulletin d'Information. Vol. 3 no. 1 (July), no. 2 (November), 1985 (Folder 19)
      - Discussion Bulletin/Bulletin de Discussion
        - Vol. 1 no. 1 (December), 1977 (Folder 20)
        - Vol. 1 no. 7 (December), no. 10 (December), 1978 (Folder 21)
        - Vol. 2 no. 4 (February), no. 8 (February), no. 9 (March), 1979 (Folder 22)
        - Vol. 6 no. 1 (April), no. 2 (May), no. 3 (June), no. 4 (June), no. 6 (July), no. 7 (July), no. 8 (July), no. 9 (July), no. 10 (July), no. 11 (July), 1986 (Folder 23)
      - Information Bulletin (Box 60)
        - Vol. 7 no. 1 (July), no. 2 (August), no. 3 (November), no. 4 (November), no. 5 (December), no. 6 (December), 1985 (Folder 1)
        - Vol. 8 no. 1 (February), 1987 (Folder 2)
        - Vol. 10 no. 1 (May), 1989 (Folder 3)
  - Chile (Box 30)
    - 1941 (Folder 1)
    - 1942-1944 (Folder 2)
    - 1945 (Folder 3)
    - 1946 (Folder 4)
    - 1947-1951 (Folder 5)
    - 1954 (Folder 6)
    - 1955-1956 (Folder 7)
    - 1959-1961 (Folder 8)
    - 1963-1966 (Folder 9)
  - China
    - 1934-1935 (Folder 10)
    - 1940 (Folder 11)
    - 1941 (Folder 12)
    - 1946 (Folder 13)
    - 1947 (Folder 14)
    - 1948 (Folder 15)
    - 1949 (Folder 16)
    - 1950 (Folder 17)
    - 1951 (Folder 18)
    - 1953 (Folder 19)
    - 1954 (Folder 20)
    - 1955 (Folder 21)
    - 1964-1966 (Folder 22)
    - 1973-1976 (Folder 23)
    - 1980-1989 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Colombia (Box 30)
    - General
      - 1976 (Folder 24)
      - 1977 (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - 1978 (Folder 6)
      - 1981-1982 (Folder 7)
      - 1983 (Folder 8)
      - 1985 (Folder 9)
    - Partido Socialista Revolucionario
      - Boletín Interno. Unnumbered (April 8), two unnumbered (May), no. 1 (May), 1985 (Folder 10)
      - Combate Socialista. No. 50, (1985 May 1) (Folder 11)
  - Costa Rica. Includes material on the Fourth International investigatory commission into the case of Fausto Amador (Box 30)
    - 1976 (Folder 25)
    - 1977 (Box 60)
      - February-March (Folder 12)
      - May-August (Folder 13)
      - September-December (Folder 14)
    - 1978 (Folder 15)
    - 1979 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - 1981-1982 (Folder 2)
  - Cuba (Box 30)
    - General
      - 1934-1936 (Folder 26)
      - 1937 (Folder 27)
      - 1938 (Folder 28)
      - 1940 (Folder 29)
      - 1941 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - 1942 (Folder 2)
      - 1943 (Folder 3)
      - 1944 (Folder 4)
      - 1945-1947 (Folder 5)
      - 1948-1949 (Folder 6)
      - 1960 (Folder 7)
      - 1961 (Folder 8)
      - 1962 (Folder 9)
      - 1964-1965 (Folder 10)
    - Partido Bolchevique Cubano. Printed cards, n.d (Folder 11)
    - Partido Obrero Revolucionario
      - Boletín Interior. Vol. 1 no. 1, (1946 March (Folder 12)
      - Cuba Obrera., 1940-1941 (Folder 13)
        Vol. 1 no. 2 (1940 October), no. 3 (November), no. 4 (December); vol. 2 no. 1 (1941 June), no. 2 (July), no. 3 (August)
      - Revolución Proletaria., 1944-1946 (Folder 14)
        Vol. 1 no. 1 (1944 May 1), no. 2 (June 1), no. 3 (July 15), no. 4 (September 15), no. 5 (October 31), no. 6 (December 31); vol. 2 no. 1 [sic] (1945 January 31); vol. 1 no. 7 Partido Obrero Revolucionario(1945 February 28), no. 8 (March 31); vol. 2 no. 1 (1945 May 1), no. 2 (June 12), no. 3 (July 8), no. 7 (November 30), no. 8 (December 31), no. 9 Partido Obrero Revolucionario(1946 April 1)
      - Pamphlet. La Voz Revolucionaria del Trotskismo en el III Congreso Nacional Obrero, 1942 (Folder 15)
    - Partido Obrero Revolucionario (Trotskista)
      - Revista Marxista Latinoamericana. Unnumbered, (1962 October) (Folder 16)
      - Voz Proletaria
        - Vol. 1 no. 1 (April), no. 2 (June 28), no. 3 (September), no. 4 (October), no. 5/6 (November/December), 1960 (Folder 17)
        - Vol. 2 no. 7 (January/February), no. 8 (March), no. 9 (April), 1961 (Folder 18)
        - No. 10 (September), supplement (October 1), supplement (October 23), no. 12 (October second fortnight), no. 14 (November first fortnight), no. 15 (November second fortnight), no. 16 (December first fortnight), 1962 (Folder 19)
        - No. 20 (February first fortnight), no. 21 (February second fortnight), no. 22 (March first fortnight), no. 23 supplement (March), no. 25 (April second fortnight), no. 27 (May second fortnight), no. 28 (June first fortnight), no. 29 (June second fortnight), no. 31 (July second fortnight), unnumbered (August 5), no. 32 (August first fortnight), no. 40 (December second fortnight), 1963 (Folder 20)
        - Translations of selected articles, 1960-1961 (Folder 21)
      - Pamphlet. A. Ortiz, Programa de Transición para la Revolución Cubana, 1960 (Folder 22)
    - Miscellany (Box 32)
      - Dialéctica. Vol. 1 no. 6 (December), no. 7 Partido Obrero Revolucionario(1938 January), no. 11 (May), 1937 (Folder 1)
      - Repartidor. Vol. 1 no. 1, (1938 August) (Folder 2)
      - Junco (Sandalo) assassination. Broadsides and clippings, 1942 (Folder 3)
      - Non-Cuban Posadas group publications. Printed articles, leaflets and circulars re Cuba, 1959-1963 (Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous printed matter, 1948-1961 (Folder 5)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1949-1968 (Folder 6)
  - Denmark, 1947-1953 (Folder 7)
  - Dominican Republic
    - 1961-1962 (Folder 8)
    - 1980 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Egypt, 1943-1948 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - France
    - General
      - 1934 (Folder 10)
      - 1935 (Folder 11)
      - 1936 (Folder 12)
      - 1938 (Folder 13)
      - 1939
        - January-June (Folder 14)
        - July-December (Folder 15)
      - 1940-1941 (Folder 16)
      - 1944 (Folder 17)
      - 1945 (Folder 18)
      - 1946 (Folder 19)
      - 1947 (Folder 20)
      - 1948-1949 (Folder 21)
      - 1950-1951 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - 1952 (Folder 2)
      - 1953 (Folder 3)
      - 1954 (Folder 4)
      - 1955-1959 (Folder 5)
      - 1960 (Folder 6)
      - 1961 (Folder 7)
      - 1962-1963 (Folder 8)
      - 1966-1968 (Folder 9)
      - 1969 (Folder 10)
      - 1970 (Folder 11)
      - 1972 (Folder 12)
      - 1978 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - 1981 (Folder 5)
      - 1985 (Folder 6)
      - 1989 (Folder 7)
    - Centre d'Etudes et de Recherches sur les Mouvements Trotskyste et Révolutionnaires Internationaux. Cahier (no. 5-8, n.d.) (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Groupe Bolchevique-Leniniste
      - Conference documents, 1935 September (Folder 14)
      - Trotskisme (No. 2, 1955 October-November) (Folder 15)
    - Ligue Communiste. Bulletin Intérieur
      - Unnumbered unnumbered Ligue Communiste(1934 July), (1932 November) (Folder 16)
      - No. 1, (1968 January) (Folder 17)
    - Ligue Communiste Révolutionnaire (Box 61)
      - Comité Central meetings, 1985 March. Notes and summaries of proceedings. Includes Courrier du Comité Central no. 57 (March 19), no. 58 (March 22), no. 59 (March 28), no. 61 (March 29), unnumbered (March 31) (Folder 8)
      - Critique Communiste supplements
        - No. 50 (March), no. 52 (May), no. 53 (June), no. 57 (November), 1986 (Folder 9)
        - No. 59 (February, 4 volumes), no. 61 (March), 1987 (Folder 10)
      - Dossier Rouge. No. 24 first quarter), (1988 (Folder 11)
      - Publications. Pamphlet and leaflets, 1985-1988 (Folder 12)
    - Parti Communiste Internationaliste (Box 33)
      - Bulletin Intérieur. No. 1, (1966 December) (Folder 18)
      - Educational materials, 1955-1962 (Folder 19)
    - Union des Communistes Internationalistes. Bulletin de Contact. New series no. 1, (1946 July) (Folder 20)
    - Miscellany
      - Pamphlet. Erwin Wolf [pseud. Nicolle Braun], "L'Organe de Masse", 1936 (Folder 21)
      - Summaries and bibliographies. Summaries of internal documents, and memoranda by Jean van Heijenoort and John G. Wright re French section in 1930s and 1940s; bibliographies of French section issuances (Folder 22)
      - Printed matter, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Germany (Box 33)
    - General
      - 1941 (Folder 23)
      - 1943 (Folder 24)
      - 1944 (Folder 25)
      - 1945 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - 1946 (Folder 2)
      - 1947 (Folder 3)
      - 1948 (Folder 4)
    - 1950 (Folder 5)
      - 1951-1952 (Folder 6)
      - 1970 (Folder 7)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Internationale Kommunisten Deutschlands. Neue Internationale. No. 2, (1947 May) (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous printed matter, Includes Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands report on clandestine activities in Nazi Germany, 1936-1939 (Folder 9)
  - Great Britain
    - General
      - 1938 (Folder 10)
      - 1939 (Folder 11)
      - 1940 (Folder 12)
      - 1941 (Folder 13)
      - 1942 (Folder 14)
      - 1943
        - January-September (Folder 15)
        - October-December (Folder 16)
      - 1944
        - January-May (Folder 17)
        - June-December (Folder 18)
      - 1945 (Box 35)
        - January-August (Folder 1)
        - September-December (Folder 2)
      - 1946 (Folder 3)
      - 1947 (Folder 4)
      - 1948 (Folder 5)
      - 1949 (Folder 6)
      - 1950 (Folder 7)
      - 1951 (Folder 8)
      - 1953-1959 (Folder 9)
      - 1961 (Folder 10)
      - 1967 (Folder 11)
      - 1968 (Folder 12)
      - 1969 (Folder 13)
      - 1970 (Folder 14)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - 1987 (Folder 16)
    - International Marxist Group (Box 36)
      - Minutes, 1967-1971 (Folder 1)
      - Internal Bulletin., 1966 July (Folder 2)
      - Circulated internal documents
        - 1965-1966 (Folder 3)
        - 1967 (Folder 4)
        - 1968 (Folder 5)
        - 1969 (Folder 6)
        - 1971 (Folder 7)
        - 1980 (Box 61, Folder 17)
        - 1982 (Folder 18-19)
        - 1985 (Folder 20)
      - Publications. Pamphlets and newspaper articles, 1982-1984 (Folder 21)
    - International Socialism Group. Internal Bulletin., 1969 August/September (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Left Fraction
      - Internal Bulletin. New series no. 5, (1945 June) (Folder 9)
      - Circulated internal documents
        - 1942-1944 (Folder 10)
        - 1945-1947 (Folder 11)
    - Revolutionary Communist Party
      - Fusion conference documents, 1944 March (Folder 12)
      - Internal Bulletin. Unnumbered (1944 August 9); new series no. 1 (1945 March) (Folder 13)
      - Circulated internal documents
        - 1944 (Folder 14)
        - 1945
          - January-August (Folder 15)
          - September-December (Folder 16)
        - 1946 (Folder 17)
        - 1947 (Box 37, Folder 1)
        - 1948 (Folder 2)
        - 1949 (Folder 3)
        - 1950 (Folder 4)
    - Revolutionary Socialist League
      - Internal Bulletin. Unnumbered, unnumbered (August), 1957 (Folder 5)
      - Leninist. No. 1, (1942 April) (Folder 6)
      - Circulated internal documents, 1939-1943 (Folder 7)
    - Workers' International League. Flyers, 1943 (Folder 8)
    - Workers Socialist League (Box 62)
      - Circulated internal document, 1978 (Folder 1)
      - Newspaper articles, 1978-1979 (Folder 2)
    - Miscellany (Box 37)
      - International Bulletin., 1962 (Folder 9)
        Vol. 1 no. 20 (1962 April 29), no. 21 (May 10), no. 22 (May 18), no. 23 (May 25), no. 24 (June 1), no. 25 (June 8), no. 26 (June 17), no. 27 (June 24, hand-corrected from no. 26), no. 28 (July 2), no. 29 (July 10), no. 30 (July 18), no. 31 (July 27), no. 34 (August 17), no. 35 (August 24), no. 36 (September 3), no. 39/40 (October 3), no. 41 (October 10), no. 42 (October 17), no. 44 (October 17), no. 46 (November 10), no. 48 (November 24), no. 49 (December 3)
      - Militant., 1942-1944 (Folder 10)
        New series no. 9 (1942 September), no. 10 (October); new series no. 8 (1943 December/1944 January); new series no. 4 (1944 September)
      - Socialist Outlook. Vol. 1 no. 4 (1949 March); special supplement (1950 July) (Folder 11)
      - Workers'Voice., 1945 (Folder 12)
        No. 3 (1945 August), no. 4 (September), no. 5 (October), no. 6 (November), no. 9 (1946 February), no. 10 (March), no. 11 (April)
      - Miscellaneous printed matter
        - 1942-1973 (Folder 13)
        - 1985-1986 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Subject file (Box 37)
      - Archival sources. Registers, 1975-1976 (Folder 14)
      - History. Lecture transcript, n.d (Folder 15)
      - Rex vs. Tearse et al. Transcripts of legal proceedings and related items re trial of Revolutionary Communist Party members for leadership of an illegal strike, 1944 (Folder 16)
  - Greece (Box 38)
    - General
      - 1945 (Folder 1)
      - 1946 (Folder 3)
      - 1947-1948 (Folder 3)
      - 1966-1972 (Folder 4)
    - Diethnistiko Epanastatiko Komma Elladas. Ergatiko Metopo. April 9, 30, May 15, 1945 (Folder 5)
    - Ergatiko Diethnistiko Komma Elladas. Ergatike Pale. Vol. 1 no. 8 (1945? June 30) (Folder 6)
  - Guyana, 1946 (Folder 7)
  - India
    - 1938-1939 (Folder 8)
    - 1941 (Folder 9)
    - 1942-1943 (Folder 10)
    - 1944 (Folder 11)
    - 1945 (Folder 12)
    - 1946 (Folder 13)
    - 1947 (Folder 14)
    - 1948-1949 (Folder 15)
    - 1950-1953 (Folder 16)
    - 1954-1956 (Folder 17)
    - 1957-1959 (Folder 18)
    - 1960-1963 (Folder 19)
    - 1969-1976 (Folder 20)
    - 1981-1983 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Indonesia (Box 38)
    - General, 1948-1956 (Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous printed matter, 1948-1965 (Folder 22)
  - Iran
    - General